{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "She ____ a message after lunch (to send)",
      "options": ["will sends", "will send.", "will sended", "will sending"],
      "correctAnswer": "will send."
    },
    {
      "question": "They ____ him tomorrow (not/to see)",
      "options": [
        "will not seen",
        "will not saw",
        "will not seeing",
        "will not see."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will not see."
    },
    {
      "question": "When ____ they ____ their answer ? (to give)",
      "options": [
        "will / gave",
        "will / give",
        "will / given",
        "will / giving"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will / give"
    },
    {
      "question": "____ you ____ me the documents tomorrow ? (to bring)",
      "options": [
        "Will / brung",
        "Will / bring",
        "Will / bringing",
        "Will / brings"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Will / bring"
    },
    {
      "question": "She ____ him. (not/to forgive)",
      "options": [
        "will not forgives",
        "will not forgiving",
        "will not forgive.",
        "will not forgave"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will not forgive."
    },
    {
      "question": "Where ____ we ____ tomorrow? (to meet)",
      "options": [
        "will / met",
        "will / meet",
        "will / meeting",
        "will / meets"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will / meet"
    },
    {
      "question": "I ____ next month. (to get married)",
      "options": [
        "will got married",
        "will gets married",
        "will get married.",
        "will getting married"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will get married."
    },
    {
      "question": "____ they ____ a new car next year? (to buy)",
      "options": [
        "Will / buying",
        "Will / bought",
        "Will / buy",
        "Will / buys"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Will / buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sindy ____ to the party without me. (not/to go)",
      "options": [
        "will not gone",
        "will not go.",
        "will not going",
        "will not goes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will not go."
    },
    {
      "question": "____ he ____ me this book? (to lend)",
      "options": [
        "Will / lending",
        "Will / lends",
        "Will / lend",
        "Will / lent"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Will / lend"
    },
    {
      "question": "When ____ you ____ a new job? (to start)",
      "options": [
        "will / starting",
        "will / starts",
        "will / start",
        "will / started"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will / start"
    },
    {
      "question": "We ____ him tomorrow. (to call)",
      "options": ["will calling", "will calls", "will call.", "will called"],
      "correctAnswer": "will call."
    },
    {
      "question": "____ Rachel ____ a cake for us? (to bake)",
      "options": [
        "Will / baking",
        "Will / baked",
        "Will / bakes",
        "Will / bake"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Will / bake"
    },
    {
      "question": "They ____ next week. (to move)",
      "options": ["will moving", "will move.", "will moved", "will moves"],
      "correctAnswer": "will move."
    },
    {
      "question": "What ____ you ____ for dinner? (to cook)",
      "options": [
        "will / cooking",
        "will / cooked",
        "will / cooks",
        "will / cook"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will / cook"
    },
    {
      "question": "She ____ a message after lunch (to send)",
      "options": ["will sends", "will send.", "will sended", "will sending"],
      "correctAnswer": "will send."
    },
    {
      "question": "They ____ him tomorrow (not/to see)",
      "options": [
        "will not seen",
        "will not saw",
        "will not seeing",
        "will not see."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will not see."
    },
    {
      "question": "When ____ they ____ their answer ? (to give)",
      "options": [
        "will / gave",
        "will / give",
        "will / given",
        "will / giving"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will / give"
    },
    {
      "question": "____ you ____ me the documents tomorrow ? (to bring)",
      "options": [
        "Will / brung",
        "Will / bring",
        "Will / bringing",
        "Will / brings"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Will / bring"
    },
    {
      "question": "She ____ him. (not/to forgive)",
      "options": [
        "will not forgives",
        "will not forgiving",
        "will not forgive.",
        "will not forgave"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will not forgive."
    },
    {
      "question": "Where ____ we ____ tomorrow? (to meet)",
      "options": [
        "will / met",
        "will / meet",
        "will / meeting",
        "will / meets"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will / meet"
    },
    {
      "question": "I ____ next month. (to get married)",
      "options": [
        "will got married",
        "will gets married",
        "will get married.",
        "will getting married"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will get married."
    },
    {
      "question": "____ they ____ a new car next year? (to buy)",
      "options": [
        "Will / buying",
        "Will / bought",
        "Will / buy",
        "Will / buys"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Will / buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sindy ____ to the party without me. (not/to go)",
      "options": [
        "will not gone",
        "will not go.",
        "will not going",
        "will not goes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will not go."
    },
    {
      "question": "____ he ____ me this book? (to lend)",
      "options": [
        "Will / lending",
        "Will / lends",
        "Will / lend",
        "Will / lent"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Will / lend"
    },
    {
      "question": "When ____ you ____ a new job? (to start)",
      "options": [
        "will / starting",
        "will / starts",
        "will / start",
        "will / started"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will / start"
    },
    {
      "question": "We ____ him tomorrow. (to call)",
      "options": ["will calling", "will calls", "will call.", "will called"],
      "correctAnswer": "will call."
    },
    {
      "question": "____ Rachel ____ a cake for us? (to bake)",
      "options": [
        "Will / baking",
        "Will / baked",
        "Will / bakes",
        "Will / bake"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Will / bake"
    },
    {
      "question": "They ____ next week. (to move)",
      "options": ["will moving", "will move.", "will moved", "will moves"],
      "correctAnswer": "will move."
    },
    {
      "question": "What ____ you ____ for dinner? (to cook)",
      "options": [
        "will / cooking",
        "will / cooked",
        "will / cooks",
        "will / cook"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "will / cook"
    },
    {
      "question": "I ____ your umbrella. (not / to take)",
      "options": [
        "did not took",
        "did not take",
        "did not taken",
        "did not taking"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "did not take"
    },
    {
      "question": "The teacher ____ us a lot of homework last week. (to give)",
      "options": ["gave", "give", "gived", "giving"],
      "correctAnswer": "gave"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who ____ you ____ yesterday? (to see)",
      "options": ["did / seen", "did / see", "did / saw", "did / seeing"],
      "correctAnswer": "did / see"
    },
    {
      "question": "____ he ____ the light? (to turn on)",
      "options": [
        "Did / turning on",
        "Did / turned on",
        "Did / turn on",
        "Did / turns on"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Did / turn on"
    },
    {
      "question": "We ____ our report yesterday. (not/ to finish)",
      "options": [
        "did not finishes",
        "did not finishing",
        "did not finish",
        "did not finished"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "did not finish"
    },
    {
      "question": "How often - you - write letters?",
      "options": [
        "How often do you write letters?",
        "How often did you write letters?",
        "How often does you write letters?",
        "How often you do write letters?"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "How often do you write letters?"
    },
    {
      "question": "It - not - late",
      "options": [
        "It does not late",
        "It not is late",
        "It is not late",
        "It did not late"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "It is not late"
    },
    {
      "question": "I - not - want to see you.",
      "options": [
        "I do not want to see you",
        "I does not want to see you",
        "Do I not want to see you",
        "I not want to see you"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "I do not want to see you"
    },
    {
      "question": "Your sister - work in the hospital?",
      "options": [
        "Does your sister work in the hospital?",
        "Do your sister work in the hospital?",
        "Did your sister work in the hospital?",
        "Your sister does work in the hospital?"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Does your sister work in the hospital?"
    },
    {
      "question": "She - sing well.",
      "options": [
        "She sings well",
        "She sing well",
        "She is sing well",
        "She do sing well"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "She sings well"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bill and Tim - not - go to bed early.",
      "options": [
        "Bill and Tim do not go to bed early",
        "Bill and Tim does not go to bed early",
        "Bill and Tim did not go to bed early",
        "Bill and Tim not do go to bed early"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Bill and Tim do not go to bed early"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why - they here?",
      "options": [
        "Why are they here?",
        "Why they are here?",
        "Why do they here?",
        "Why did they here?"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Why are they here?"
    },
    {
      "question": "It - hot.",
      "options": ["It is hot", "It does hot", "It do hot", "It did hot"],
      "correctAnswer": "It is hot"
    },
    {
      "question": "What - you - like about London?",
      "options": [
        "What do you like about London?",
        "What does you like about London?",
        "What you do like about London?",
        "What did you like about London?"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "What do you like about London?"
    },
    {
      "question": "My friend - study French",
      "options": [
        "My friend studies French",
        "My friend study French",
        "My friend does study French",
        "My friend studying French"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "My friend studies French"
    },
    {
      "question": "We - home alone.",
      "options": [
        "We are home alone",
        "We do home alone",
        "We does home alone",
        "We did home alone"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "We are home alone"
    },
    {
      "question": "They - from Canada?",
      "options": [
        "Are they from Canada?",
        "Do they from Canada?",
        "Does they from Canada?",
        "Did they from Canada?"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Are they from Canada?"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jack - read books in Spain?",
      "options": [
        "Does Jack read books in Spain?",
        "Do Jack read books in Spain?",
        "Did Jack reads books in Spain?",
        "Jack does read books in Spain?"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Does Jack read books in Spain?"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kate - not - interested in science.",
      "options": [
        "Kate is not interested in science",
        "Kate not is interested in science",
        "Kate does not interested in science",
        "Kate did not interested in science"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Kate is not interested in science"
    },
    {
      "question": "People - eat ice cream in hot weather.",
      "options": [
        "People eat ice cream in hot weather",
        "People does eat ice cream in hot weather",
        "People do eat ice cream in hot weather",
        "People eating ice cream in hot weather"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "People eat ice cream in hot weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "When - they - skate?",
      "options": [
        "When do they skate?",
        "When did they skate?",
        "When does they skate?",
        "When they do skate?"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "When do they skate?"
    },
    {
      "question": "Her children - happy.",
      "options": [
        "Her children are happy",
        "Her children do happy",
        "Her children does happy",
        "Her children did happy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Her children are happy"
    },
    {
      "question": "We - not - tired.",
      "options": [
        "We are not tired",
        "We do not tired",
        "We does not tired",
        "We did not tired"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "We are not tired"
    },
    {
      "question": "How - he?",
      "options": ["How is he?", "How do he?", "How does he?", "How did he?"],
      "correctAnswer": "How is he?"
    },
    {
      "question": "They - not - drink coffee at all.",
      "options": [
        "They do not drink coffee at all",
        "They does not drink coffee at all",
        "They did not drink coffee at all",
        "They not drink coffee at all"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "They do not drink coffee at all"
    }
  ]
}
